streeteasy.com 2013-05-21

# StreetEasy: Privacy Policy Search

StreetEasy is concerned about protecting the privacy of all of our web site visitors. We respect your privacy and your choice not to have your personal information shared with other people. Please read the following to learn more about our policy. Your use of our web site indicates your acceptance of this Privacy Policy.

### Collection Of Information

StreetEasy does not collect personally identifying data, such as names, addresses, email addresses, and the like, except when voluntarily submitted by web site visitors.

For non-registered users, StreetEasy does not collect personally identifying data from site visitors. For registered users, we only collect personally identifiable information which you provide. This information is normally provided when you (a) register as a user of the site; (b) send us email or (c) choose to receive emails from StreetEasy.

The personally identifiable information which you provide is used only to customize the content and advertising which you see, and for us to contact you by email when you have authorized us to do so.

Non-personally identifiable information is used anonymously and in the aggregate for us to conduct research and to improve the performance and compatibility of our services. This information includes technical information such as browser type, computer platform, as well as click-stream information, searches performed and other website activities which we record and analyze in the aggregate.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://adwords.google.com/support/aw/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100746).

### Transmission Of Information

All credit card and billing information transmitted to StreetEasy.com website from your browser is encrypted using SSL 2.0 or SSL 3.0. Any communication with a third party for billing or credit card verification will be encrypted with SSL 2.0 or equivalent encryption. 

### Disclosure Of Information

StreetEasy will not disclose or share any personal information you provide to us with any other party without your permission, except if requested to do so in accordance with a court order, subpoena, or similar legal order, or in the event such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of StreetEasy, its users, and other third parties. StreetEasy will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

### Links

StreetEasy may provide links to other third party web sites, and other web sites may provide links to the StreetEasy web site. Third party web sites operate according to their own terms of use and privacy policies. StreetEasy has no control over such third party web sites, and therefore you acknowledge and agree that StreetEasy is not responsible for the availability of such third party sites, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites. You further acknowledge and agree that StreetEasy will not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites.

### Children

StreetEasy does not solicit personal information from children. You must be 13 years or older to use this site.

### Changes To Our Policy

StreetEasy may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on this page or if you are a registered user we may notify you by email at the primary address which you have provided.

### Terms of Use

Use of this web site is subject to our Terms of Use. By using this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions contained therein.

### Contact

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, our online practices, or your dealings with this web site, please send email to [**support@streeteasy.com**](mailto:support@streeteasy.com)

StreetEasy  
13 Crosby St, 2nd Floor  
New York, NY 10013  
+1 212 804 6884
